锁定
解锁
没时间慢慢来了
No time for niceties.
你不能小点声吗 Luthor?
Way to be stealthy, Luther.
我把激光防护网关掉的时候,警报就已经发出去了
The moment I shut down the laser grid, it sent a silent alarm.
他们已经在过来的路上了
They're already on their way here.
射!
Dibs.
量子启动器!
The quantum trigger.
现在机会在我们手上了
Now we have a chance.
跑!
Run.
那挡不了他们多久
That's not going to slow them down for long.
根本就挡不住......
That's not gonna slow them down at all.
你在等什么?
What are you waiting for?
快啊!
Hurry.
逗乐的时间结束了  Lex.
It's time to get serious, Lex.
不!我们可以一起走! 我们能成功的!
No. We can make it together. We can do this.
带着你那亮闪闪的光头走吧 我的眼睛都被晃疼了
Get your shiny bald head out of here. It's hurting my eyes.
我能说什么?
What can I say?
好吧!好吧!
Okay, okay.
我要讲我这辈子最后一个笑话了!
I'm down to my Last Joke, anyway.
这可是个致命的笑话!
But this one will kill you.
你不会白死的 老朋友
It won't be in vain, old friend.
Luthor!
ULTRAMAN: Luthor.
你觉得你能在我的超能视觉面前藏起来吗?
You think you can hide from my ultra-vision?
你会为你所做地事付出代价 我保证
You're gonna pay for what you've done, mate.
我也保证...
-That's a promise. -I've gotta a promise of my own.
我会把Jester(注:正义版小丑)的工作做完
I'm going to finish the Job the Jester started.
但不是现在
But not Just yet.
正义联盟 两个地球的危机
要是我也在上面 我想我们能快不少
The work would go a lot faster if l were up there with you, guys.
耐心点 我就快帮你准备好了
Patience. I'm almost ready for you.
这些得花多少钱,Bruce?
How much is all this costing, Bruce?
我不喜欢考虑钱的问题
I don't like to think about it.
好了,Flash. 现在开始测试
All right, Flash. Beginning test run.
我不知道? 蝙蝠侠 你不觉得有点快吗...
l don't know, Batman. This is pretty radical.
你确定没问题吗?
You're absolutely sure it works?
蛮确定的
Pretty sure.
蛮确定?我觉得...
Pretty sure? That isn't--
...还不行吧!
--good enough.
传输成功
TeIeporter's online.
你疯了吗?! 他是疯了吧?!
Are you crazy? Is he crazy?
他自己都没谱 怎么能拿我做实验?!
How could he use that thing on me if he wasn't sure?
- 他就是开个玩笑.  是吗? 你怎么知道?
-He was Joking. -Yeah, how can you tell?
你真觉得他会在没把握的时候拿你的小命冒险吗?
You really think he would risk your life if he wasn't sure?
好吧...也许...
Well, maybe.
我的意思是 我觉得他不是很喜欢我
I mean, I don't think he likes me very much.
我不觉得他会"很喜欢"任何人
I don't think he likes anyone very much.
早上好
Good morning.
哪个好心人能告诉我
Would you be kind enough to tell me
最近的警察局在哪儿?
where I could find the nearest police station?
不好意思  我有件很紧急的事...
Excuse me, it's very important that I--
好好好 你先冷静一下 这儿是警察局
Yeah, yeah. Cool your Jets.
这儿任何事都很重要... Luthor?!
This is a police station. Everything's important he--Luthor
没必要这么紧张
No need to make a scene.
我只需要你们帮我联系正义联盟
I want you to contact the Justice League for me.
- 其他? - 呃 我不知道...
Or else? Oh, I don't know.
我会摧毁全世界? 这样够了吗?
I'll destroy the world? Is that sufficient?
超人 请说
Superman. Go ahead.
我们有麻烦了 是你的老朋友
BATMAN: We've got a problem.One of yours.
大家放松 从现在起由我们负责
It's okay. We'll take it from here.
亏他们还叫我Flash 注:Flash有露阴的意思
Oh, and they call me The Flash.
- 你以为自己在干什么? - 我有话要说
-What do you think you're doing? -I've come to talk.
你能看得到  我可是手无寸铁
As you can see, I'm not armed.
你会很难相信我所说的话
You're going to find what I have to say very difficult to believe.
你是从平行宇宙里的地球上来的
You're from a parallel Earth.
你怎么可能知道?!
How could you possibly know that?
你的内脏位置都反了
Your internal organs are reversed,
心脏在另一边
your heart is on the wrong side.
- 可能是个陷阱 - "可能是"
It could be a trick.Could be.
但我们的Luthor还呆在Striker岛上的小监房里
But our Luthor's still in his cell on Stryker's Island.
既然你们已经清楚我不是那个Luthor
And now that we've clarified the matter of my evil twin...
我可以开始讲我的故事了吧
...I've got quite a story to tell you.
裤子
Pants.
我们的世界绝大部分都很相似
My world is similar to yours in many ways
但在某些方面非常不一样
but very different in others.
等等 等等 你先别告诉我!
Oh, wait, wait, don't tell me.
在你的世界里 是你在领导正义联盟?!
On your world, you're the leader of the Justice League.
某种意义上说 我曾经是
As a matter of fact, I was.
"曾经是"
Past tense.
我不仅仅是正义联盟的领导者
I'm not Just the Leader of my world's Justice League.
我还是唯一的幸存者
I'm its only surviving member.
我们被一群超能力者各个击破
We were systematically destroyed by a group of superpowered beings
他们的名字 叫作"罪恶集团"
...known as the Crime Syndicate.
他们聚集在一起很多年了 为所欲为
They've run rampant for years, doing whatever they pleased.
他们用恐惧统治人类
They rule through fear...
随时都会用他们的超能力来对付普通民众
...occasionally turning their powers
只为提醒我们服从统治
against the populace, Just to remind us.
为了不至于造成大面积的恐慌
In the hope of maintaining some minimal order...
各国领袖都假装不存在这些人
...the authorities simply pretend they aren't there.
但他们越来越拒绝被忽略
But increasingly, they refuse to be ignored.
"罪恶集团"已经完全胁迫了人类领袖
The Syndicate has completely intimidated civil authority.
警察不会逮捕他们
The police won't arrest them...
即使逮捕了 检察官也不会控告他们
...and prosecutors wouldn't press charges if they did.
唯一可以迫使他们
The only thing keeping them from completely
不能完全取代政府的
overthrowing the government...
只有核打击的威胁
...is the threat of a nuclear response.
你们 就是我的世界最后的希望
You people are my world's last hope.
我们得讨论一下
We have to discuss this.
请在外面等候
Please wait out here.
- 我不信任他 - 我一点也不吃惊...
-I don't trust him. -There's a surprise.
也许真的黑白颠倒了
Maybe he's on the up and up.
你自己说地 他不是我们的Luthor
You said yourself, he's not our Luthor.
无论如何 没一个Luthor我喜欢的
Still, never met a Luthor I liked.
我对他读心了 他讲地是实话
I've read his mind, he's telling the truth.
更何况我们有责任去拯救他
Regardless, we have a responsibility...
那个世界里的万千生命
to the millions of people being oppressed on his world.
听着 在我获得超能力之前 我不过是个小警察
For all my power, when it comes down to it, I'm a beat cop.
做事得按规矩来
There are rules.
另一个次元里的地球也许就不是我们的辖区了
Another dimension may be out of our Jurisdiction.
我不敢相信你们还要讨论?
I can't believe we're having this discussion.
我们当然得帮他!
Of course we're going to help.
她说的对 我们应该这么做
She's right. That's what we do.
这次不行
-Not this time.
为什么?
-Why not?
我们还有很多事没做完
We've got too much on our plate right here.
我们的新基地都还没建好
We haven't even finished constructing our new headquarters.
我们的第一责任是保护地球
Our first responsibility is to protect the Earth.
你说得对 "我们"的地球
That's right. Our Earth.
我们现在的人手可能连这个地球都保护不好
We don't have enough manpower to even do that properly.
够了 我们在讨论地是亿万人的生命
Fair enough. But we're talking about millions of people.
我们不能拒绝他们 我们得去
We can't Just turn our backs. We have to go.
Luthor 我们决定帮你
All right, Luthor, we'll help.
但我们需要一个计划
But we need a plan.
我正好有一个计划
I have one, of course.
什么让你这么着迷?
What's so fascinating?
Luthor解决了量子去相关的问题
Luthor has solved the decoherence problem.
亲爱的 除非跟钱有关
Darling, unless there's money involved,
否则你还是让我觉得无趣
you're still boring me.
平行宇宙里的地球
Parallel Earths.
Luthor不仅证实了它的存在
Luthor is not only proven they exist...
他还想出了在平行宇宙中穿行的方法
...he's figured out how to travel between them.
找到量子启动器了吗?
Any sign of the quantum trigger?
我们把这儿都翻遍了 那玩意肯定已经不在这儿了
We've searched the entire complex. If it was here, it's not now.
不错 把这些资料全都下载到我的电脑里
Download all these records into my personal computer.
其余的人
The rest of you,
找找这儿还有什么有用的东西
strip this place of anything useful,
然后毁了这儿
then destroy it.
抱歉可能有点晕
This could be disorienting,
我还没来得及修理...
but there are no other side effects that--
见什么鬼?!
What the hell?
- 我找到帮手了! - 你们完蛋了
We're compromised. What tipped you off
没时间跟他们纠缠了 我要那些数据
I don't have time for this. I need that data.
解决他们
Take them down.
够了!
That will be enough of that.
我很擅长给别人调弦
-That's what I call tuning somebody up.
不好意思...
WOMAN: Excuse me.
我能跟你聊会吗?
Can I talk to you for a minute?
赫拉!(详见神奇女侠系列)
Hera.
这种把戏我早就玩过了
I've played this game before.
你不想和我战斗 你只想帮我
You don't wanna fight me.You wanna help me.
我不想和你战斗 我只想...
I don't wanna fight you, I want....
嘿 这怎么跟杰迪武士的原力洗脑一样的?
Hey, this is like the Jedi mind trick.
这不是杰迪武士的原力洗脑
This is not like the Jedi mind trick.
抱歉
Sorry.
住手!
J'ONN J'ONZZ: Stop that.
我们得撤了
We've got to retreat.
为什么?我们赢了
Why? We're winning.
女超人已经叫了援兵
Superwoman's called in the cavalry...
如果我没估计错 我想我们还没准备好对付他们
...and if it's who I think it is, we're not prepared.
别跟我们客气 我们可不是来做客的
Don't make us guess. What are we in for?
至少三个"战友" 每个都和女超人实力相当
At least three Made Men, almost as tough as Superwoman.
- 战友? - 等会再说!
-Made Men? -Later.
我没时间跟你解释了   跟着我
I don't have time to explain. Follow me.
见鬼!
FLASH: Oh, crap.
我来接着你
GREEN LANTERN: I've got you.
小心!
Heads up.
更多麻烦来了!
More trouble.
离我的飞机远点
Get off my plane.
夜枭的飞机上是自己人吗?
Is that one of us in Owlman's plane?
是两个自己人 神奇女侠在驾机
Two of us. Wonder Woman swiped it.
那也许我们有办法摆脱这些麻烦了 绕着我飞行
Then there may be a way out of this. Swing around for me.
你来对付他 飞机归我
Stay on top of him. The plane is mine.
- 在哪儿?  - 你在找什么?
Where is it? What are you looking for?
隐形按钮 我吃过那个的苦头
Chameleon circuit. Owlman used to drive me crazy--
找到了!有什么效果?
Found it. What's it do?
绿灯 我们隐形了 就在你们上方
Lantern, we're cloaked right above you.
靠过来吧 我们就在这儿
Hold fire, our ride's here.
坐稳了!
-Hang on. -Whoa!
攻击那片云!
Strafe the skies.
- 太妙了  - 没关系
Well, that's fried.
我们还是隐形的
It doesn't matter, we're still cloaked.
我们甩掉他们了 至少目前是
WONDER WOMAN: And we've lost them. At least for the moment.
那么 现在去哪儿?
So, genius, where to now?
冷静!
Come to order.
首要之急:
First business.
我们得决定谁来代替
We've gotta decide
Jarkus的位置(Jarkus邪恶版火星客 )
who we're calling up to replace J'arkus.
愿他安息
God rest his soul.
他们的组织里没有领袖 也没什么人才
There's no managerial talent in that organization.
我们应该解散他们 然后瓜分他的地盘
We should dissolve them and spilt up his territory.
说地好啊!
Right,
你早就把火星客的手下当成你的自助餐了
seems to me you've already helped yourself to the Martian's crew.
还好早上我没死在那帮人的手上
You had the whole bunch this morning.
"战友"需要首领来管理
Made Men need to be associated with one of the family heads...
如果你想要 那些人也可以归你
...if you want some of them.
瓜分人手的事可以以后再说
We can horse-trade for manpower any time.
地盘呢?
-What about the turf?
我同意夜枭 我们五个人瓜分一切
I'm with Owlman. We'll divide his action between the five of us.
什么时候轮到你说话了?
Who died and made you boss?
想掰掰腕子吗?
You wanna arm wrestle for it?
别闹了!
Knock it off.
我们稍后再讨论细节
We'll work out details later.
从现在起火星客(Jarkus)的人归夜枭管
For now, Owlman can keep J'edd J'arkus' guys.
我觉得我们可不止需要这么点人手
From what I hear, sounds like you could have used a few dozen more
Luthor弄来了正义联盟的人 不能小看
Luthor's new Justice League is not be underestimated.
不错 他们会对我们反击的
Neither are we. They'll fold.
是我们会反击他们
Or we'll fold them.
就像任何挡在我们路上的人一样
Just like everybody else who gets in our way.
我们将到达权利的顶端
Which brings us to the topic at hand.
上次会议
Last meeting,
六大成员里的五个通过了一个项目
five of six family heads approved of Project Damocles.
于是我开始建造了这个
Per our vote, I have begun construction on this,
一个量子本态炸弹
the quantum eigenstate device.
一旦完成...
Once completed,
我们就将拥有整个星球的生杀大权
the QED will give us life-and-death power over the entire planet.
去年我们花了370亿给各国政府 以后没有了
We spent 37 billion on government bribes last year.
我们就是全世界的政府!
No more of that. We'll be the government.
我还是不明白?
I still don't see why they
怎么让他们把仅存的一点政权献给我们
would give up the little bit of power they got left.
因为如果他们拒绝 我们就会启动这个
Because if they don't, we'll do this.
在海森伯格的装置会在
The device's Heisenberg uncertainty override...
全球爆发出难以限量的毁灭能量
allows us to tap into a limitless pool of destructive energy.
这将让政府们面对这样一个选择:
Which leaves the governments of the world with two choices:
要么屈服 要么灭亡!
Bow down to us or die.
最重要的是首先要记住!
ROSE: The most important thing to remember...
我们没必要害怕"罪恶集团"
...is we don't have to be afraid of the Crime Syndicate.
你要真这么觉得还带保镖干嘛?
REPORTER: If that's true, why do you have bodyguards?
拜托!我是总统的女儿!
Come on, my father's the president.
这些保镖在我开始公开演说之前就跟着我了
I had guards before I started speaking out.
你不觉得自己很不负责任吗?
Isn't it irresponsible of you to be out here making speeches...
你所说的与你父亲的政策完全冲突
...in direct contradiction of your father's policies?
我爱父亲 但我们对此意见不同
I love my father, but we disagree about this,
而我拥有发表言论的自由!
and I have the right to free speech.
我们与"罪恶集团"说不定可以井水不犯河水
If we leave the Syndicate be, they'll Let us live our lives.
我们没有足以击败他们的能力
-We don't have the power to fight them. -No.
"说不定"不足为据!
Might doesn't make right.
也许眼前看起来是这样
It may seem that way, but in the long run...
但长远来看一定是截然相反的!
...it's the other way around.
只要我们做出正确的选择 我们就比想象中更强大!
We are always stronger when we're doing the right thing.
开灯
LEX: Lights.
这儿的装修不错啊
I love what you've done with the place.
这儿不是我的 曾经是我一个朋友的
LEX: It's not mine. It used to belong to a friend.
对不起 Harley
I'm sorry, Harley.
Jester(注:正义版小丑)永远不会回来了
The Jester's never coming back.
我们应该感到幸运还有这么个藏身之所
We should consider ourselves lucky there's any place left to hide.
我们来这儿不是为了藏身的,Luthor
We're not here to hide, Luthor.
我们是来收拾这儿的残局的
We're here to clean up your planet's mess.
无论怎么样 现在我们可以开工了
Then by all means, let's get started.
你可以叫我 Lex
And call me Lex.
这些就是领头的
These are the big guns, the heads of the six.
六个首领......现在只有五个了
I should say, five families.
奥特人(邪恶版超人)是首领中的首领
Ultraman is the boss of bosses,
但他们都属于同一个组织
but they all front formidable organizations.
其他的那些超能力者呢?
Where do all those superpowered guys fit in?
每个首领手下都有上千的
LEX: Each of the family heads...
犯罪者给他们工作
have thousands of criminals working under them.
他们会选出最值得信任的恶棍...
They reward their most trusted
并赋予他们超能力
lieutenants by giving them superpowers.
他们被称为"战友"
They're called Made Men.
这名字真可爱 有多少人?
Cute. How many?
每个人下面不会超过7到8个
LEX: No more than seven or eight at a time.
加起来也许有50人
Perhaps 50, total.
由我指挥 我们会发起一系列攻击
We'll conduct a series of attacks, coordinated by me.
我们六个人将对选定的"罪恶集团"行动进行打击
The six of us will hit specific Syndicate operations...
逐个击破
...one after the other.
- 那太浪费时间了! - 你说什么?!
-That's a waste of time. -I beg your pardon?
我们将一次对多个目标进行打击
We're going to hit multiple targets at the same time.
- 两人一组  - 我们会在人数上占极大劣势的!
Teams of two. We'd be hopelessly outnumbered.
别忘了我的正义联盟
-When my Justice League fought them--
我尊重他们 Lex...
-All due respect, Lex.
但我们才是你的正义联盟
We aren't your Justice League.
- 怎么分组? - 你和John(火星客)一组
-What's the call? -You and J'onn.
Dinan(神奇女侠)和绿灯一组 他跟我一组
Diana and GL. He's with me.
这太疯狂了
That's insane.
别担心 Lex 他会让你很放松的
-Don't worry, Lex. He's got your slack. -Flash.
- Flash! - 呃 我说的是实话啊
Well, you do.
你来之前应该先给我打个电话
You're supposed to call first.
我要是不能想来就来
What's the point of having your keys
还要你的钥匙干嘛?
if I can't drop in unexpectedly?
还在找量子启动器吗?
Still Looking for the quantum trigger?
是 不过同时...
Yes, but in the meantime,
我还发现一些同样有趣的事情
I've been working on something equally interesting.
我们可以用这个在平行宇宙间来回
We can use it to travel to any of the alternate Earths.
我在Luthor设计的基础上做了些改进
It's based on Luthor's design.I've made some improvements.
你知道有了这个对我们意味着什么吗?
Do you realize what we could do with this?
当然他的哲学意义是非常重大的
The philosophical implications are tremendous, of course.
哲学?
Philosophy.
这代表着有无数个地球等着我们去征服!
There's an infinite number of Earths out there to conquer.
就我们两个 不用与任何"集团"里的人分享!
You and me.We wouldn't have to share our cut with the Syndicate.
当然这也是一种可能
That's certainly one way to go.
没办法了 弃船吧
-Right, then. Abandon ship if you can. -Oh! Oh!
- 我来对付她! - 不
-I got her. -No.
她归我!
She's mine.
奥特人 我知道你能听见我说话
Ultraman, I know you can hear me.
你这虚张声势的家伙是自己滚出来......
Bring your arrogant ass out here
还是我们进去请你出来?
or we'll come in and get you.
我们不是来找他的打手的,Olsen
Not Looking for the hired help, Olsen.
我要找你的老板!
I want your boss.
他不在这儿
He ain't here.
你可以给秘书打电话预约
If you want an appointment, you can call his secretary.
从我们的领空里滚开
Clear our airspace.
你可以求我
Make me.
你不走 我就请你走
I can do that.
他交给你 我去找奥特人
You take care of Ultraman's pal. I got the big guy.
我其实不想伤害你  Jimmy
I'd rather not have to hurt you, Jimmy.
你确定要跟他打吗?
You sure you want to do this?
我可以对付他
I can take him.
你们迟早会走 击败他对我意义重大
If it's going to mean anything after you're gone, it has to be me.
放了我的手下!
Get your hands off my boy.
你先救你自己吧!
You've got problems of your own.
你太狂妄了,Lex
Getting cocky, Lex?
你以为你能跑到我的地盘上撒野
You think you can come to my place
还能在我头上动土!
of business and call me out?
你忘了我是谁了吗?
Did you forget who I am?
你忘了我是怎么做上老大中的老大的?
How I got to be the boss of bosses?
我能站在这儿 因为我是恶中之恶!
I'm here because I'm the baddest of the bad.
任何挡在我路上的人 都得死!
Anybody whoever stood in my way is dead.
任何人!
Everybody.
我给你... 准备了礼物
I brought you  a present.
- 蓝氪石!  - 唯一能克制你的东西
Blue kryptonite. The only thing that can hurt you.
但我...
But I--
毁了地球上的所有氪石?
Destroyed the last piece on Earth?
不错 不过别忘了我去过另一个地球了
True. But I've been visiting other Earths.
你迟早会感到非常非常后悔的!
You are so gonna regret this.
我有条消息要跟你宣布 大人物
Got a message for you, big man. Things are changing.
一切都在改变 当你做了错事......
When you do wrong...
会有越来越多的人不惧纠正你们!
there are more and more of us who aren't afraid to set it right.
美国机密局
United States Secret Service.
总统有话跟你们说
The president would like a word with you.
我无法接受,Lex! 你以为自己在干吗?
This is unacceptable, Lex. -What do you think you're doing?
我想这很明显 总统先生
LEX: That should be obvious, Mr. President.
我们在收拾坏人 先生
We're taking it to the bad guys, sir.
是啊 你们该感到自豪
Well, you should be very proud.
你们想过哪怕那么一下
Have you given the slightest thought to
你们的行为会有什么后果吗?
the consequences of your actions?
别把我当成小孩
Don't talk to me like a child.
我在你的政权向"罪恶集团"屈服之前
I was fighting this battle long before your administration
就在与他们战斗了
decided to roll over for the Syndicate.
我们没有屈服
We didn't roll over.
我们在努力与"罪恶集团"
We've worked to achieve a delicate balance
维持一个微妙的平衡
with the Crime Syndicate.
这是唯一可以让美国人民过上相对安宁生活的办法
It's the only way the American people can live in relative safety
抱歉 总统先生 但你说的都是屁话!
Forgive me, Mr. President, but that's a load of crap.
无论如何 我已经下令释放奥特人了
Be that as it may, I've already ordered the release of Ultraman.
你干了什么?!
You did what?
你最好注意你的口气
You wanna watch your tone?
抱歉 总统先生
I'm sorry, Mr. President.
我不明白你怎么能这么白白放走他们
I Just don't understand how you could Let them go free.
很明显你对什么都不明白
You clearly don't understand much of anything.
你以为有人敢出庭作证吗?
Do you think anybody would testify against the Crime Syndicate?
就算有人敢跟"罪恶集团"作对
Do you think if anybody were willing,
我们能保护证人的生命直到出庭吗?
we could keep them alive until trial?
- 我们可以 - 是吗?
-We can. -Oh?
你能同时也保护证人家人的安全吗?
Are you going to protect their families too?
你能待在这儿守护我们一辈子吗?
Are you going to stay here and watch over us forever?
当然不可能 但我们现在就能阻止他们
Obviously not.
永远地终结他们的犯罪行为
But we can stop them right now. Put an end to their hold over you.
杀了他们?
Kill them?
不 我们不杀人
No. We don't do that.
那我有个更好的主意
WILSON: Then I've got a better idea.
你们不如回家去收拾你们自己星球上的犯罪者去吧!
Why don't you go home and end all crime on your own planet?
你怎么就不能长点骨气!
Why don't you grow a backbone.
- 现在别添乱,Rose.  - 你能躲到什么时候 爸爸?
Not now, Rose. Then when, Dad?
- 这是个机会!  - 那不过是做梦!
We've got a chance.That's a fantasy.
跟这些人作对 就必须得拿无辜民众的生命冒险
We can't fight these guys without risking the lives of millions.
上帝啊 爸爸 您曾经是个战争英雄啊!
ROSE: My God, Dad.You were a war hero.
什么时候变成个孬种了?
When did you turn into a coward?
他不是个孬种 越是经历过残酷战争的人...
J'ONN J'ONZZ: He is not a coward.
就越是懂得生命的可贵
...are often among those who hold life most dear.
你怎么知道我在想什么?
-How did you know what I was thinking?
这是个意外 我不是故意对你读心的
-It was an accident. I didn't mean to read your mind.
- 我...  - 在我的星球上有一种说法
There's a saying on my world:
恶势力最大的成功
''The only thing necessary for the triumph
便是让好人无所作为
of evil is for good men to do nothing.''
像你这样的人要好勇斗狠当然很容易
It's easy for someone like you to be brave.
但大多数人可不是刀枪不入的
But most of us aren't bulletproof.
先生 一直以来我所对抗的犯罪者大多比我更强大
Sir, I stand up to guys more powerful than I am all the time.
你也一样能做到
You can do the same.
听上去很简单 哈?
That simple, huh?
对不起 总统先生...
I'm sorry, Mr. President,
但我们不会放弃
but we're not about to give up this fight.
尤其是当我们看到胜利的希望时
Not when we finally have a chance to win it.
- 你不是应该在帮忙吗?  - 我在帮忙啊
-Aren't you supposed to be helping? -I am helping.
我在改善一下气氛
I'm improving the ambiance.
很好 我正计划这么做来着
In a way, that's what I'm planning to do.
说到底 要是没有引爆器 要炸弹有什么用?
After all, what good is a bomb if you don't detonate it?
你从来没准备拿量子炸弹当勒索信来使吧?
You never had any intention of using the QED for bIackmall.
你想用它杀掉所有人
You're going to use it to kill everybody.
是又如何?
What if I am?
- 告诉我 为什么?  - 为什么不?
Just tell me. Why? Why not?
我是认真的
I'm serious.
我是个变态杀人狂 那是我的魅力来源
I'm a murdering psychopath. It's part of my charm.
我认同这一点
I do find it attractive.
但你从不做没理由的事
But you never make a move without a reason.
你为什么想要毁掉全世界?
Why would you want to destroy the world?
因为这是我唯一的选择
Because it's the only action one could take
没有任何理由
that would have any purpose.
这样我就不能认同你了
You Lost me there.
我们所做的每一个决定 都是毫无意义的
Every decision we make is meaningless...
因为在平行宇宙里的某一个地球上
...because somewhere, on a parallel Earth,
我们已经做出了相反的选择
we have already made the opposite choice.
我们一无所有
We're nothing.
微不足道
Less than nothing.
你怎么能这么说?
How can you say that?
我们富有 我们是征服者
We're rich. We're conquerors.
这个地球上我们贫穷 我们是奴隶
And here we're poor. We're slaves.
这个地球上 我们的父母从未相遇
And here, our parents never met,
我们根本就没出生
so we were never born.
这儿 世界在一场核战争中毁灭了
Here, the world ended in nuclear war.
这儿 没有一条鱼敢于跨上陆地
Here, no fish was ever brave enough to crawl up on land...
物种甚至完全没有进化出人类
...and humans never evolved.
不止于此 无穷无尽
And so on, ad infinitum.
所以即使你毁了这个世界
So even if you destroy the world,
还有亿万个同样的 是吗?
there are a billion others, right?
又有什么区别呢?
What difference would it make?
在多元宇宙里的某一处
Somewhere in the multiverse,
我将那儿称为"第一地球"
there is a world I call Earth Prime.
所有的平行地球都来源于此
Every Earth is a variation of this one, the original.
只要我将这里毁灭了
And once I destroy it,
所有的平行地球都会毁灭
all reality will follow.
我收回我说过的话
I take it back.
你比我疯狂多了
You're much crazier than I am.
别挡我的道
Don't get in my way.
正相反
To the contrary.
我要帮你
I'm in.
- 我猜我能在这儿找到你  - 我不想和你说话
I thought I might find you here.
那就听我说
-I'm not talking to you. -Then listen.
你必须停止那些针对"罪恶集团"的演说
You're going to have to stop speaking out against the Syndicate.
至少不在公共场合
At Least in public.
你知道吗 当我还是个小女孩的时候
You know, when I was a little girl,
你就是我的英雄
you were my hero.
你怎么了?
What's happened to you?
也许我们都长大了
Maybe we both grew up.
小孩很麻烦吧
ULTRAMAN: Kids, huh?
我们想尽办法保护他们 他们却总是让你抓狂
They drive us crazy, but we'd still do anything to protect them.
我说地对吧?
Am I right?
你想怎样?
What do you want?
你的宝贝女儿经常上新闻啊
Saw your daughter on the news the other night.
- 她有张能说会道的嘴啊  - 这是个自由的国家
-She's got a mouth on her. -It's a free country.
你我都非常了解
We both know better than that.
你最好管教好你的小姑娘 要不然我会替你管教的
You get your little girl under control, or I'll do it for you.
还记得第一夫人的遭遇吗?
Remember what happened to the First Lady.
你敢靠近我的女儿 我就会使用核武器!
If you come near my daughter, I will nuke you.
你听明白了吗!
You hear me?
是啊是啊 核武器
ULTRAMAN: Yeah, the nukes.
确实是不错的制约手段啊
-Great equalizer, huh? -Uhn!
听我跟你说 总统先生
Well, Let me tell you something, Mr. President.
我的手下正在制造一颗更厉害的炸弹
My boys are working up a bomb of our own.
你这儿不错 我会喜欢住在里面的
Nice place.I think I'm gonna like it here.
我又开始觉得无聊了
I'm getting bored again.
- 你找到"第一地球"了吗?  - 还在找
Did you find Earth Prime? Still Looking.
不过我找到了些其他的东西
But I found something else.
Luthor将量子启动器放在了一个平行地球上
Luthor took the quantum trigger to a parallel Earth.
你能帮忙  去我们的隔壁
Would you be a dear pop over to the
地球上把那玩意取回来吗
universe next door and pick it up for me?
安全传感器
联网
警告
入侵者
COMPUTER VOICE: Perimeter breach. Potential intruder alert.
潜在入侵者警告
Perimeter breach. Potential intruder alert.
就在这儿 分散 找到它
It's here. Spread out and find it.
你闯入了我的地盘
You're on my property.
滚出这儿
Stand down.
你进入我的管辖区了
You're in over your head.
在我伤到你之前赶紧退后
Back off before I come over there and hurt you.
螳臂当车
Insect.
呆那儿别动了 你就一个人
Stay down. You're outnumbered.
你最好再数一次
Count again.
你们有麻烦了
You guys are in trouble.
拿下他们
Take them.
小心海王子(Aquaman) 他们比你强壮
Careful, Aquaman. They're stronger than you are.
那可未见得
That remains to be seen.
好吧 比我想地要麻烦一些
Okay, this is gonna be tougher than I thought.
想听秘密吗?
Wanna hear a secret?
你倒是有些能耐啊 小家伙
You've got possibilities, little man.
很可惜 我没时间跟你玩了
But, sadly, I don't have time to play with you.
我们走!
Let's go.
- 把这个拿给夜枭  - 是
-Take this to Owlman. -Yes, mistress.
他怎么办?
What about him?
恐怕我得在他身上花点功夫了
Oh, I'm sure I'll think of something.
我们为同一个原因聚集于此
ROSE: We're all here for the same reason. We're tired.
我们厌倦了!厌倦于生活在恐惧中!
Tired of living in fear.
厌倦于我们选举出的政府向万恶的罪犯屈服!
Tired of our elected officials bending over for vicious criminals.
一切大可不必如此!
It doesn't have to be that way.
今天 你们可以与我一起
Joining me today are elected officials
选举出一个不屈服的政府!
who aren't afraid to act.
法官 检查官 警察
Judges, prosecutors, police officers...
以及每一个同你们一样勇敢的普通人!
...and brave people like each and every one of you.
同心协力我们可以做到!我们......
Together we can win. Together we--
抱歉
Excuse me.
不!离我远点!
No. Stay away from me.
你保护我多久了?
How Long have you been watching me?
抱歉没有告诉你
My apologies for the deception.
我不认为他们会停止对你的暗杀
I doubt this will be the Last attempt.
如您允许 我将继续贴身保护你
With your permission, I'll continue to keep close watch on you...
直到度过当下的危机
...until the immediate crisis has passed.
那很好
That would be Just fine.
身手不错
Nice moves.
你让我想起了我的男朋友
You remind me of my boyfriend.
我该拿你怎么办呢?
Whatever will I do with you?
我可以用这个把你送走
I could use this to send you away.
也许这儿不错
Perhaps to here...
这个地球上的人类都进化成了
...an Earth where humanity has mutated into
可怕的夜行生物
hideous creatures of the night.
不 搞不好你会很喜欢那儿
No. You might like that.
这儿有个不错的地方
Oh. Here's a good one.
一个冰冷 无人居住的地球
A cold, uninhabited Earth,
你会慢慢地死去
where you'll slowly starve to death...
如果你没一下子被冻硬的话
...if you don't freeze first.
也许就这么让你苟延残喘会更有趣
Or it might be fun to keep you as a pet.
来 让我来为你搬开它
Here. Let me do that.
现在该你了
-Your call. -Sorry.
抱歉你不是我的菜
You're not my type.
礼尚往来 我会折断你一根肋骨的
That's going to cost you a rib.
我实在是喜欢骨头折断的那一声
I like my lovers to make a little noise.
我还能再折断些什么呢?
What else can I break?
你以为一些烟雾弹就能让你在我面前藏身了?
You think you can hide from me with a smoke bomb?
那不是烟雾弹
BATMAN: It's not smoke.
是麻醉毒气
It's anesthetic gas.
蝙蝠侠呼叫正义联盟
Batman to Justice League.
你确定那个能锁住她吗?
You sure that will hold her?
你在我的卫星上藏了什么东西?
-What did you hide on my satellite?
我不知道你在说什么
-I don't know what you're talking about.
那是什么宝贝那么值钱?
What was so valuable that the Crime Syndicate...
"罪恶集团"穿越平行宇宙也想要拿到!
...would cross dimensions to get it?
- 没被她得手吧?  - 无论那是什么
-Did you keep it from her? -Her henchman escaped with it.
- 他的小喽啰带着它逃走了  - 那是量子启动器
Whatever it was.It's the quantum trigger,
用来启动他们正在建造地炸弹
the detonator for a bomb they're building.
没有那玩意 我们可以与他们战斗 但现在......
Without it, we could fight them, but now--
- 你干嘛不直接毁了那东西?  - 那是纯能量体
Why didn't you Just destroy it?It's pure energy.
无法被毁灭
It can't be destroyed.
好吧 他们已经得手了 最坏的情况是什么?
Okay. They've got it.What's the worst-case scenario?
他们可以用启动器来引发爆炸
They could use it to set off an explosion
那将毁灭整个地球
that would wipe out the entire Earth.
可不止整个地球袄
You think too small.
- 女超人哪儿去了?  - 也许只是放我们鸽子了
Where's Superwoman?Probably Just blowing us off.
- 早知道我也这么干  - 我们不会再等了
Like I should have.We're not waiting anymore.
我们开始会议
Let's get started.
人们不像以前那么好吓唬了
People aren't as intimidated as they used to be.
也许我该下去 在大街上来个"快速"扫荡之类的
I should go down for a Jog and terrorize the straights.
就连执法部门都开始跟我们对着干了
Even regular law enforcement's starting to show some backbone.
奥特人都进过一趟局子了
Archer got himself arrested.
公众已经渐渐不再为炸弹的威胁所屈服了
Public opinion wouldn't be an issue if the bomb were ready.
量子本态炸弹就快完成了
The QED is nearly complete.
我已经派人出去搜寻最后的组件了
I have agents out gathering some equipment.
对不起 抱歉没获经允许就进来
Sorry, sorry to come in without permission...
但女超人说这个一定要交给你
...but Superwoman said to bring this right to you.
你没必要变形
You don't have to wear that disguise.
这儿没人能看见你
No one can see in here.
我以为这样能让你舒服一点
I thought it would make you more comfortable.
正相反
Just the opposite.
我希望了解真实的你
I'd like to get to know the real you.
好多了
That's better.
- 你真的是从火星上来的?  - 是的
-Are you really from Mars? -Yes.
所有火星人都会读心术吗?
And can all Martians read minds?
曾经是 我是火星最后的幸存者了
Could. I am the Last survivor.
我为我之前对你的读心行为道歉
I apologize for reading your mind before.
未经允许的读心是极端不礼貌的
It is considered extremely impolite to do so without permission.
我不介意
I didn't mind.
那种感觉......我不知道......很自然
It seemed, I don't know, natural.
我们之间联通了
We are attuned.
我们的思想同步率达到了某种程度
Our minds are in sync to a degree
这即使在我们火星人之间也很罕见
that was rare even among my own people.
我从未想到我会遇到一个人类
I never imagined I'd meet a human
与我有如此高的默契
so complimentary to myself.
我感觉到了......这种联通......
I feel it, attuned.
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
试着吻你
Trying to kiss you.
在地球上 这是一种分享情感的方式
On Earth, it's a way of sharing affection.
在火星上 我们这样做
This is how we do it on Mars.
感受我
Know me.
那感觉 WOW......
That was.... Wow.
现在 我们了解彼此了
Now we know each other.
正义联盟打了那么多胜仗
All the battles the Justice League have won.
你相信你们能击败"罪恶集团"吗?
You think you can beat the Crime Syndicate?
只要我们能找到他们 我并不怀疑
If we could find them, I have little doubt.
我能找到他们的基地在哪儿
I could find out where their base is.
我父亲很多年前就知道了
My father's known for years.
能搭个手吗?
You wanna give us a hand here?
最后的计算 我需要非常专心
Final calculations. Very delicate.
扫描 结果:不吻合
我们到了没?
FLASH: Are we there yet?
你已经说了15遍了 从头到尾一点也不好笑
That wasn't funny the first 15 times you said it, either.
尽情享受最后的人生吧
Enjoy yourselves while you can.
我的朋友们会把你们撕个粉碎的
-My friends are going to tear you apart.
我早说过我们不该带上她
-Told you we should have Left her.
我们不能冒险留下她
We couldn't take the chance she'd escape
她可能会提前预警我们的袭击
and warn them we're coming.
等我重获自由 杀了蝙蝠侠之后 第一个就杀你
When I get loose, I'm killing you right after Batman. Uhn!
带着你不代表我非得听你废话
Doesn't mean we have to listen to her, though.
我们该怎么再混进去?
How are we supposed to get in again?
多频率绑定时间分析复制包
Multi-frequency band, encryption analyzer-replicator pack.
不是每个人都能听懂鸟语的......
Some of us don't speak Star Trek.
你就把它当成一个很酷的车库开门器好了
Think of it as a fancy garage-door opener.
老兄 可以把你那个没用的废物零件装进去了
Come on, then. Pitch in, you miserable git.
你还得搞多久啊?
JOHNNY QUICK: Having a kip, are we?
我跟你说话呢
I'm talking to you.
舱门刚被打开了
The hangar doors Just opened.
只有我这么觉得吗?你们不觉得太简单了吗?
Is it Just me, or does this seem a little too easy?
我们正要去找你们
We were Just about to come Looking for you.
量子炸弹已经安装好了 你们最好投降吧
The QED is armed now. You'll want to surrender.
你们听见了 炸弹在我们手上
ULTRAMAN: You heard him. We've got the bomb.
每个人照我们说的做 否则......
Everybody does what we say, or else.
少吹牛了 只要炸弹还在这儿
You're bluffing.
你们总不能炸了自己的老巢
As Long as the bomb's here, all you can blow up is your own house.
也许该投降的是你们 我们已经抓住了几个你们的同党
Maybe you should surrender. We've taken down dozens of you.
现在的局面是 我们6 你们3
And now the odds are 6-to-3.
再数一遍
SUPERWOMAN: Count again. -Uhn! Uhn!
我在舱门那儿发现了她
Look who I found in the hangar.
认输吧!
Submit.
巴嘎(注:为毛讲了句日语)
Bugger.
扫描
覆盖被拒绝
第一地球
不!
No.
发生了什么?
-What Just happened?
他把量子炸弹带到"第一地球"去了
-He's taken the QED to Earth Prime.
如果他引爆炸弹 所有平行世界都将被摧毁
If he detonates it, he'll destroy all reality.
- 听上去可不妙啊  - 别听他胡说
-I'm not liking the sound of that. -Don't listen to him.
夜枭只不过是把炸弹藏起来而已
Owlman's Just taking the bomb to a hiding place.
别想耍我 你们俩干了什么!
Don't try and con me. What are you two doing?
不可能追踪到他了 已经结束了
LEX: There's no way to follow him.
还没有
-It's over. -Not yet.
这个量子启动器的存储器里能记住几个目标地点?
How many coordinates does this thing keep in memory?
- 只有最后几个移动目标 但......  - 足够了
The Last dozen or so, but--That's more than enough.
目标:第一地球
夜枭早料到了 我们被他算计了
Owlman's way ahead of us. We're locked out.
除非......
Unless....
有人能以恰好等于夜枭载波的速度保持振动
Someone vibrating at the right speed could piggyback...
那样 就能打开一条通道
...on Owlman's carrier wave and open a portal.
但那个人必须要足够快
But he'd have to be fast.
- 我就是你要找的人  - 不 你不是 你太慢了
-I'm your man. -No, you're not. You're too slow.
- 你说什么?
-What?
我知道你的极限
-I know your limitations.
你还不足以快到启动通道
You can't possibly reach the speed necessary to pull this off.
我可以
-But I can. -Listen.
- 听着...  - 不 你听着
-I-- -No, you listen.
这可是关系到整个世界的事 我不会让我的世界被毁灭的
He's talking about my world. I'm not letting that happen.
可能会很危险
-It could be dangerous--
看在这见鬼的宇宙的份上 我当然知道会危险了
-The bloody universe is at stake.Of course it's dangerous.
好 当你达到恰当的速度时
All right, when you reach the proper speed,
我会给你个信号
I'll give you a mark.
你必须精确地保持那个速度
LEX: You have to hold that speed precisely.
明白了吗?
Got it?
再快一点
Faster.
再快一点!
目标锁定
保持这个速度!
Hold that speed.
我是下一个
I'm next.
你没有传送设备
You don't have a transit device.
你会被黑洞边界(事界)隔绝在外面的
You'd be torn apart by the event horizon.
欢迎来到"第一地球"
OWLMAN: Welcome to Earth Prime.
这个地方 在任何思想之前便存在了
Before there was thought, there was this place.
想象一下 在一个单一的历史中
One Earth, with a single history.
人类的出现带来了自由意志的幻想
But with the coming of man came
伴随着这个幻想
the illusion of free will...
混乱也随之而来
...and with that illusion came chaos.
我们所做出的每一个选择
With every choice we make,
理论上都会创造出一个平行世界
we literally create a world.
历史一分为二
History branches in two,
当我们做出选择 一个世界诞生
creating one Earth where we made the choice...
当我们没有做出选择 则诞生另一个世界
...and a second where we didn't.
你知道吗?那就是这个宇宙的秘密
That's the secret of the universe, you know.
亿万人 做出亿万选择
Billions of people making billions of choices...
从而创造出无限多的地球
...creating infinite Earths.
有些地球很相似
Some so similar to each other
你花一辈子也找不出什么不同的地方来
you can spend a lifetime searching for any distinction,
而有一些则完全不同
others so radically different...
它们可以逆转一切的定义
...they defy comprehension.
每一个分支都来源于这个地球
And all of the branches originate here.
现实的每一个版本都恰好在
Every version of reality balances precariously
这个唯一的地球上取得微妙的平衡
on this singular Earth.
它看上去与我们所知道的地球如此不同
It seems so different from the Earths we know.
我很难想象 最初在这个第一地球上
I can't imagine what series of decisions led
什么样的决定让这个世界渐渐远离正确的轨道
to this world hurtling out of its orbit.
但我知道
But I know this:
一切灾难的根源永远还是那一个
The source of the cataclysm was the same as it always is.
人类
Man.
你无法确定这一点
You can't be sure of that.
- 任何事......  - 你比我清楚
-Anything-- -You know better.
人类就像癌症一样
Man is a cancer.
而我选择永远地切除这一毒瘤
And I've chosen to cut out the disease.
- 你是说你要杀掉......  - 每一个曾经存在过的人类
You're talking about killing--
以及将要存在的人
Everyone who ever lived. Who ever will live.
序列锁定 放弃:是/否
我选择做出唯一的真实存在的选择
I choose to make the only possible real choice.
你疯了
You're insane.
没关系
Does it really matter?
还有很多平行的"我"
There are alternate versions of me
你总能找到一些你喜欢的
that you would find quite charming.
据我所知 我们其实很相似
OWLMAN: From what I gather, we're very much alike.
关于你的每一件事都证实这一点
Everything about you tells the tale.
你的姿态 你的面具 你的装备
Your attitude, your costume, your tactics...
都在尖叫
...they all scream
带着愤怒 绝望 焦虑
of outrage, despair, vengeance.
究竟发生了什么可怕的事情让你走上了这条道路
What terrible wrong was done to set you on this path?
其实也没关系
It doesn't really matter.
任何事情都没关系
Nothing matters.
你打算怎么办?
What are you planning to do,
讲话讲死我吗?
talk me to death?
事实上......
Actually....
我准备打到你死!
I thought I'd beat you to death.
你该让你那位会飞的朋友过来的
You should have sent your flying man.
他的力量或许还有一丝机会
With his strength, he might have had a chance.
但你不会将你要做的事交给任何人
But you don't trust anyone else to
你谁都不信任
do what needs to be done.
- 我也不信任任何人  - 如果我们真的很相似
Hah. I feel the same way.If we're really alike,
你便该知道不是这样的
you know this is wrong.
你至少曾有一瞬间是个好人
You must have been a good man, once.
不 我不是个好人
No. Not good.
从不
Never good.
说到底 我不过也是个普通人而已
After all, I'm only human.
搜索
争论到此为止
-Uhn! -No more debate.
现在我就杀了你
I'm going to kill you now,
然后 毁灭所有人
then everyone else.
你我之间确有不同
There is a difference between you and me.
你我都自地狱而来
We both looked into the abyss...
然而当一个救赎的机会出现时
...but when it Looked back at us...
你错过了
...you blinked.
放弃:是/否
又有什么关系~
It doesn't matter.
你还好吗?
Are you all right?
Johnny我回来了 停止振动
Johnny, I'm back. Stop vibrating.
停下来!
Stop.
上帝啊
Oh, God.
我们拯救了地球吗?
Did we save the world, then?
是的
We did.
那些扯淡的话......
And all that rubbish
关于我比Flash快那些
about me being faster than Flash?
你早就知道会变成这样
You knew this was gonna happen.
干地好
Good one, mate.
这结局真让人伤心
That's real sad, ain't it?
现在你们可以从我的基地里滚出去了
Now, get your asses off my moon.
你有毛病吗?
What's wrong with you?
- 我们几乎失去了所有  - 此一时彼一时
We almost Lost everything.That was then.
现在你们就是些想逮捕我的义务警察
Now you're a bunch of wanna be cops trying to take me in.
- 不是想要 是将要!  两件事
Going to take you in.
两件事 你没这个权利
Two things: You ain't got the authority
你也不够本事
and you ain't nearly tough enough.
我们的本事足够了
We're more than tough enough.
- 带援兵了?  - 我带来一整只部队
Brought the cavalry?I brought the Marines.
总统对于暗杀他女儿的行为
The president was displeased by the attempt
感到非常不高兴
on his daughter's life.
他们携带着核武器来了
There are nuclear weapons in the shuttle.
数量充足 人人有份
I brought enough for everybody.
大恩不言谢
WILSON: There's no way to thank you.
你们挽回了我们的世界
You've given us back our world.
我已经下令国家守卫部门
I've already ordered the national guard to
协助地方执法
support local Law-enforcement teams.
我们正在四处围剿坏人
We're rounding up the bad guys everywhere.
- 我不想你走  - 我也不想走
I don't want you to go.
但我不属于这儿
I don't want to go either, but I don't belong here.
你可以的 你可以同我一起属于这里
You could. You could belong here with me.
抱歉 John
Excuse me, J'onn,
不过你可不可以别在像个白痴一样?
but would you stop acting like an idiot?
- 什么?!  - 这不就是我们战斗的目的吗?
-What? -This is what we fight for.
爱她 你就留下
If you love her, stay.
我已经失去了一次家园
I've already Lost one home.
我曾宣誓保卫我的新家园
I made a promise to protect my new one.
那就让我们在这里说再见吧
Then this is how we say goodbye.
也许我们的地球上还有个跟她一样的姑娘
Maybe there's another one like her back on our Earth.
照我以往的运气看 她很可能是个坏人
With my luck, she'll be evil.
回家的感觉真好
Ah. It's good to be back home.
小心撞头
-Ow! -Mind your head.
我真不敢相信你把飞机带回来了
FLASH: I can't believe you kept that thing.
这是对我自己的奖励 我很喜欢它
Spolls of war. I like it.
你要飞机干嘛?你会飞
What do you need a plane for, anyway? You can fly.
- 你不也开车吗?  - 完全两回事好吗?
You drive a car.That is so not the point.
关于这次的事我欠你一个道歉 你说地对
I owe you an apology about this mission. You were right.
你也没错
We were both right.
无论如何 多找些帮手总不是坏事
Still, more help around here wouldn't be a bad idea.
我很高兴你同意我的看法
I'm glad you agree.
我一直在考虑咱们该增加些成员
I've been thinking about a membership drive.